<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on Vimarsh</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on Vimarsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fastest way to install WordPress</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/fastest-way-to-install-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/fastest-way-to-install-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I will be showing you the fastest way to install a fully functional WordPress website with an auto-renewing free SSL certificate in less than 3 commands. Let’s get started.
Prerequisites Make sure you are using Linux or Mac for installing WordPress. If you are deploying a website you might be using a virtual machine in the cloud for the same. Stay tuned for another post on how you can get 2 free VMs forever on Oracle Cloud</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience using DuckDuckGo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/my-experience-using-duckduckgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/my-experience-using-duckduckgo/</guid>
      <description>DuckDuckGo is a privacy-focused search engine that claims it does not track its users and provides organic search results and ads that are not personalized to you. This is my experience of using DuckDuckGo exclusively for almost a month.According to their own homepage:
The Filter Bubble Apart from all the privacy features, another big claim by DDG is that it helps you escape the “filter bubble”; which essentially means that Google and other similar search engines (like Bing, Yahoo) bring massively different search results for different users, even though the query is exactly the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Agriculture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/smart-agriculture-vimarsh-shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/smart-agriculture-vimarsh-shah/</guid>
      <description>Smart Agriculture Project uses agricultural robot based on machine learning to address three main issues
  Over watering,
  Early identification of plant diseases and
  Efficient monitoring of farms.  In agriculture fields, lack of proper monitoring results in low yields and unpredictable revenue. Lack of early detection of crop diseases, destroys the plants and do not leave enough time to take preventive measures. In India, 30% of crops are destroyed due to plant diseases and almost 50% water is wasted due to over watering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Old Blog Posts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>Before having this website, I used to blog and write articles on Blogger.com which can be found at oldblog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
