<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Vimarsh</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Vimarsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:36:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deceit – Why there is a 99% chance that you are deceitful.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/deceit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/deceit/</guid>
      <description>What is Deceit? WikipediaMost people expect their conversations with their close friends, family members and other strangers to be frank and honest. We feel like we are entitled to know about everything, even minute details. This enables there to trust in the other one you are talking to. But, even though we think we are being honest with a person or that person is being extremely sincere with you; it might not be the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if robots do all the work? – Finding Meaning in Life</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/what-if-robots-do-all-the-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/what-if-robots-do-all-the-work/</guid>
      <description>If robots do all the work, there won’t be any scarcity of human manpower, food, shelter and basic needs and most wants. Most people will have nothing to do, or will they?
Imagine you go to a restaurant owned by a human in that Utopia. They might be making meals and serving people because they like to do that. You do not need to pay for that service, as the basic needs are already satisfied by (non-human destructing) robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youth and Essence of Individuality👦</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/youth-and-essence-of-individuality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 18:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/youth-and-essence-of-individuality/</guid>
      <description>I have recently observed and felt that, we the children and Youth, in order to fit into a certain designed parameters often leave behind the essence of individuality. We often leave behind our unique characteristic which make us a different person and an “Individual”.
Recently I have observed that, Groupism is at its peak especially among school cultures: say you don’t like a particular thing or do not have an interest in a matter / subject – you are left out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farmer Protests Explained – The promise to increase revenue by 200%</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/farmer-protests-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 05:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/farmer-protests-explained/</guid>
      <description>The new farm laws promise to 2x yes you read that correctly the income{.rank-math-link} of farmers in the next 2 years by relying on the deregulation of the market. But most analysts and critics say this might not work and, in fact, the income of small to medium farmers (comprising 80% of the farmers) might reduce by upto 40%{.rank-math-link}. Which is a substantial hit.
If you want to directly understand the problems click here{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future conflicts will be confined to online hacking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/future-conflicts-will-be-confined-to-online-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/future-conflicts-will-be-confined-to-online-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Bots once built to brute force and gain access to accounts are now being used to create posts and comments on public forums and social media.
Below is my speech I spoke on for English Speaking Skills test.
We have all seen in movies, that a guy with a hood in a dark room, rummaging the keyboard, presses Enter and whole internet is down. He can then control and spy on people and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeopathy — Health or Hoax</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/homeopathy-health-or-hoax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/homeopathy-health-or-hoax/</guid>
      <description>A scam that actually (kind of) works!
Homeopathy — all of us might have heard about it. It is a very famous alternate form of allopathic (_normal _— as we define it) medication; in the same category as the like of Ayurveda. People mostly argue that it is “fake” and scientifically baseless, while there are some people who I personally know who praise its effectiveness and say it is very effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastest way to install WordPress</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/fastest-way-to-install-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/fastest-way-to-install-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I will be showing you the fastest way to install a fully functional WordPress website with an auto-renewing free SSL certificate in less than 3 commands. Let’s get started.
Prerequisites Make sure you are using Linux or Mac for installing WordPress. If you are deploying a website you might be using a virtual machine in the cloud for the same. Stay tuned for another post on how you can get 2 free VMs forever on Oracle Cloud</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Zoos help in Animal Conservation?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/do-zoos-help-in-animal-conservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/do-zoos-help-in-animal-conservation/</guid>
      <description>Some of the world’s best zoos offer the visitors to see in front of their eyes animal species that might be impossible for them to see in the wild, ever**.** A zoo or Aquarium visit provides an opportunity to get mesmerized by the beautiful and diverse wildlife at one place.But there are many NGOs that are anti-zoo and believe in animal rights to live in open space like CAPS &amp;amp; PETA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience using DuckDuckGo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/my-experience-using-duckduckgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/my-experience-using-duckduckgo/</guid>
      <description>DuckDuckGo is a privacy-focused search engine that claims it does not track its users and provides organic search results and ads that are not personalized to you. This is my experience of using DuckDuckGo exclusively for almost a month.According to their own homepage:
The Filter Bubble Apart from all the privacy features, another big claim by DDG is that it helps you escape the “filter bubble”; which essentially means that Google and other similar search engines (like Bing, Yahoo) bring massively different search results for different users, even though the query is exactly the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disastrous impact of Education Industry on Inspiration in Students</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/disastrous-impact-of-education-industry-on-inspiration-in-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/disastrous-impact-of-education-industry-on-inspiration-in-students/</guid>
      <description>I went to Random Word Generator and got these wordsThe topic I came up with : Disastrous impact of education Industry on Inspiration of students
What exactly is Inspiration?
anything that drives one to do, create, endeavor, begin or develop some pursuit, skill, art or start with a fire or do something creative
How is the Modern Education Industry impacting it? According to me, the modern schooling /tuition /coaching industry is negatively impacting students in having that inspiration, that DESIRE to start something new or peruse a particular hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to host a WordPress website on a VM simply</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/how-to-host-a-wordpress-website-on-a-vm-simply/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/how-to-host-a-wordpress-website-on-a-vm-simply/</guid>
      <description> Create a Ubunutu 20.04 VM Run the following commands via SSH  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Agriculture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/smart-agriculture-vimarsh-shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/smart-agriculture-vimarsh-shah/</guid>
      <description>Smart Agriculture Project uses agricultural robot based on machine learning to address three main issues
  Over watering,
  Early identification of plant diseases and
  Efficient monitoring of farms.  In agriculture fields, lack of proper monitoring results in low yields and unpredictable revenue. Lack of early detection of crop diseases, destroys the plants and do not leave enough time to take preventive measures. In India, 30% of crops are destroyed due to plant diseases and almost 50% water is wasted due to over watering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Old Blog Posts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>Before having this website, I used to blog and write articles on Blogger.com which can be found at oldblog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
