<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Article on Vimarsh</title>
    <link>http://vimarsh.info/categories/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Article on Vimarsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:36:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://vimarsh.info/categories/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deceit – Why there is a 99% chance that you are deceitful.</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/deceit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/deceit/</guid>
      <description>What is Deceit?  Deception or falsehood is an act or statement which misleads, hides the truth, or promotes a belief, concept, or idea that is not true. It is often done for personal gain or advantage. - Wikipedia
 Most people expect their conversations with their close friends, family members and other strangers to be frank and honest. We feel like we are entitled to know about everything, even minute details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if robots do all the work? – Finding Meaning in Life</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/what-if-robots-do-all-the-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/what-if-robots-do-all-the-work/</guid>
      <description>If robots do all the work, there won’t be any scarcity of human manpower, food, shelter and basic needs and most wants. Most people will have nothing to do, or will they?
Imagine you go to a restaurant owned by a human in that Utopia. They might be making meals and serving people because they like to do that. You do not need to pay for that service, as the basic needs are already satisfied by (non-human destructing) robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farmer Protests Explained – The promise to increase revenue by 200%</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/farmer-protests-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 05:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/farmer-protests-explained/</guid>
      <description>The new farm laws promise to 2x yes you read that correctly the income{.rank-math-link} of farmers in the next 2 years by relying on the deregulation of the market. But most analysts and critics say this might not work and, in fact, the income of small to medium farmers (comprising 80% of the farmers) might reduce by upto 40%{.rank-math-link}. Which is a substantial hit.
If you want to directly understand the problems click here{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homeopathy — Health or Hoax</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/homeopathy-health-or-hoax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/homeopathy-health-or-hoax/</guid>
      <description>A scam that actually (kind of) works!
Homeopathy — all of us might have heard about it. It is a very famous alternate form of allopathic (_normal _— as we define it) medication; in the same category as the like of Ayurveda. People mostly argue that it is “fake” and scientifically baseless, while there are some people who I personally know who praise its effectiveness and say it is very effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Zoos help in Animal Conservation?</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/do-zoos-help-in-animal-conservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/do-zoos-help-in-animal-conservation/</guid>
      <description>Some of the world’s best zoos offer the visitors to see in front of their eyes animal species that might be impossible for them to see in the wild, ever**.** A zoo or Aquarium visit provides an opportunity to get mesmerized by the beautiful and diverse wildlife at one place.But there are many NGOs that are anti-zoo and believe in animal rights to live in open space like CAPS &amp;amp; PETA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disastrous impact of Education Industry on Inspiration in Students</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/disastrous-impact-of-education-industry-on-inspiration-in-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/disastrous-impact-of-education-industry-on-inspiration-in-students/</guid>
      <description>I went to Random Word Generator and got these wordsThe topic I came up with : Disastrous impact of education Industry on Inspiration of students
What exactly is Inspiration?
anything that drives one to do, create, endeavor, begin or develop some pursuit, skill, art or start with a fire or do something creative
How is the Modern Education Industry impacting it? According to me, the modern schooling /tuition /coaching industry is negatively impacting students in having that inspiration, that DESIRE to start something new or peruse a particular hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Old Blog Posts</title>
      <link>http://vimarsh.info/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vimarsh.info/blog/my-old-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>Before having this website, I used to blog and write articles on Blogger.com which can be found at oldblog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
